frontrunnerpro.com 2018-04-06

# FrontRunner's Privacy Policy

## FrontRunner Professional is the funeral profession's leading technology solutions provider. We highly value our relationship with our funeral home clients and the public they serve, and respect their privacy and yours. To that end, all personal information will always be protected and will never be sold to third parties.

* * *

### __What We Collect

We may collect the following information: 

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What We Do With This Information

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### __Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### __Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### How We Use Service and Obituary Information

We allow service and obituary information to be shared across our trusted networks and affiliated websites such as ObitsforLife.com to help reach further in helping extended family and friends to be notified. Our goal is to enhance your searching, information and fulfillment experience with us through convenient and timely services. By submitting this personal information to us, you are consenting to its use and disclosure for the following purposes: 

  * Extend your comments, condolences and tributes to the families being served.
  * Meeting safety, security, legal and regulatory requirements;
  * Providing you with general service and business partner information.
  * Conducting market analysis to better serve you in the future.
  * Maintaining the accuracy of our records, in order to facilitate customer service requests and support general client communications.

If these intended uses are not reasonably obvious from the circumstances in which personal information is collected, we will provide you with an opportunity to withhold your consent to the collection, use or disclosure of the information. For example, we will give you an opportunity to tell us not to use for marketing purposes the contact information that you provide us when registering for a service. Keep in mind, however, that there are limited situations in which applicable laws require or allow us, our affiliates, suppliers, business partners and our dealers to collect, use/disclose personal information without consent. They include, for example, safety and law enforcement or compliance activities.

### Privacy Policy Template – AdWords Remarketing

This website uses Google AdWords

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the FrontRunner Professional website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/).
